<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A.I.relevant</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A.I.relevant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>surfsafetynet@gmail.com (Overlytic)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>surfsafetynet@gmail.com (Overlytic)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime: The good, the bad and the popular</title>
      <link>/post/popular_anime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>surfsafetynet@gmail.com (Overlytic)</author>
      <guid>/post/popular_anime/</guid>
      <description>As indicated in my previous post, I am going to analyse a tidy tuesday dataset for this blogpost. I will be using the R programming language and the excellent series of packages called the tidyverse.
This week’s tidy tuesday dataset is about anime, and comes from MyAnimeList.net. I find this especially exciting since I have enjoyed quite a bit of anime in my life - much to the dismay of my girlfriend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elephants don&#39;t fly</title>
      <link>/post/elephants_dont_fly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>surfsafetynet@gmail.com (Overlytic)</author>
      <guid>/post/elephants_dont_fly/</guid>
      <description>Just some motivational content that I need to externalise.
Looking at the blog&amp;rsquo;s logo, the image of Dumbo is supposed to come to mind. Even though you don&amp;rsquo;t generally explain a rather obvious logo, I think it is the easiest way to lead into the lesson I am trying to learn.
To state it simply, learning to do proper data analysis and machine learning is hard. But what I am realising more and more, is that thinking about learning it is even harder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>/post/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>surfsafetynet@gmail.com (Overlytic)</author>
      <guid>/post/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my irrelevant blog! This is the first step on a quest to master the complicated twists and turns of the machine learning world. As the blog&amp;rsquo;s slogan suggests, the goal is to learn and to keep things fun. To achieve this I will pick the most absurd and light-hearted projects I can think of!
To ensure I remain focused, I will start with short posts about the following topics:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>surfsafetynet@gmail.com (Overlytic)</author>
      <guid>/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Just a random guy trying to grow machine learning wings :)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>